Contact

9196303854 (Mobile) ninamc65@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ninamccullock-a5493b4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Surgery and Procedures ACLS

Languages

French Spanish

Certifications

Ambulatory Care Nurse Certified Case Manager

Nina McCullock

BSN, RN-BC, CCM, LNC

Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina Area

Summary

Care Manager with UNC Healthcare

Registered nurse since 1995 and perioperative nurse since 1997. Have worked at Duke, UNC Healthcare and Rex Healthcare in various perioperative and clinical areas. I was also a travel OR nurse. I am skilled in medical-surgical, preoperative, intraoperative and postoperative nursing, nursing management and utilization management. Also skilled now in case management.

I completed a course in Legal Nurse Consulting through Duke University in December 2014; that was a goal of mine for several years.

Passed my CCM exam August 2019!

Experience

UNC Health Care 5 years

Care Manager, Clinical Care Management September 2019 - Present (10 months) Chapel Hill, North Carolina

Utilization Manager, Clinical Care Management December 2017 - September 2019 (1 year 10 months) Chapel Hill, North Carolina

Clinical Nurse 3/Nursing supervisor, GI Procedures/GI Clinic July 2015 - December 2017 (2 years 6 months)

Hillsborough, North Carolina

Duke University Health System
Clinical Nurse
February 1996 - July 2015 (19 years 6 months)

Durham, North Carolina

I worked on 3300, in the North OR's, PDC, Duke Center for Aesthetic Services, and the ECT clinic. The dates above are not consecutive; I left Duke and came back twice

Convergence Medical Staffing OR travel nurse March 2015 - June 2015 (4 months)

OR Staff nurse at Roanoke Carilion Hospital, Roanoke VA

Soliant

Travel OR nurse August 2014 - March 2015 (8 months)

OR staff nurse at Carteret General Hospital, Morehead City, NC OR staff nurse at Florida Hospital, Waterman, Tavares Florida

PPR Travel Nursing
Travel OR nurse

June 2014 - August 2014 (3 months)

OR staff nurse at Novant Forsyth Medical Center, Winston-Salem, NC; helped during their Epic rollout. They went live while I was there. I had already been using Epic for a while.

UNC Health Care

Clinical nurse

February 2001 - February 2014 (13 years 1 month)

Chapel Hill, North Carolina

Several clinical areas including the main OR, PCS, ACC, PACU and the department of Orthopaedics. I did the same thing at UNC that I did at Duke; left and came back twice

Education

University of Mount Olive
Bachelor of Science - BS, Nursing · (2015 - 2017)

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Broadcast Journalism/RTVMP · (1983 - 1987)

Watts School of Nursing

Diploma in Nursing · (1994 - 1995)

Duke University

Certificate in Legal Nurse Consulting · (2013 - 2014)